<resources>
    <string name="app_name">Command</string>

    <!--Dashboard-->
    <string name="dashboard_learn">Learn</string>
    <string name="dashboard_questions">Questions</string>
    <string name="dashboard_progress">Progress</string>
    <string name="dashboard_account">Account</string>

    <string name="learn_description">These are our favorites and some of the ones we consider the most useful.</string>
    <string name="questions_description">Check your knowledge by trying our quiz of 20 questions.</string>
    <string name="progress_description">See how you improved your knowledge by the help of this application.</string>
    <string name="account_description">Manage your account here.</string>

    <!--Categories-->
    <string name="categories_misc">Miscellaneous</string>
    <string name="categories_security">Security</string>
    <string name="categories_network">Network</string>
    <string name="categories_storage">Storage</string>

    <string name="misc_description">Basic and most useful CMD commands</string>
    <string name="security_description">Essential CMD commands to ensure higher security</string>
    <string name="network_description">Essential CMD commands related to computer networks</string>
    <string name="storage_description">Essential CMD commands related to computer storage</string>

    <!--experience_level-->
    <string name="experience_level">Select your level of experience on CMD:</string>
    <string name="beginner_header">Beginner Level</string>
    <string name="intermediate_header">Intermediate Level</string>
    <string name="advanced_header">Advanced Level</string>

    <!--questions-->
    <string name="total_questions">OF 3</string>
    <string name="beginner_q_header">BEGINNER LEVEL</string>
    <string name="intermediate_q_header">INTERMEDIATE LEVEL</string>
    <string name="advanced_q_header">ADVANCED LEVEL</string>

    <!--Beginner_Q1-->
    <string name="q1">What is the correct command for creating an undeletable folder?</string>
    <string name="q1_a1">mkdir con</string>
    <string name="q1_a2">md con</string>
    <string name="q1_a3">md config</string>
    <string name="q1_a4">mkdir config</string>
    <string name="q1_number">1</string>

    <!--Beginner_Q2-->
    <string name="q2">What will happen if you enter "list disk" command on cmd?</string>
    <string name="q2_a1">PC will sleep</string>
    <string name="q2_a2">Hard disk will be formatted</string>
    <string name="q2_a3">List of disks will be shown</string>
    <string name="q2_a4">The health of the hard disk will be shown</string>
    <string name="q2_number">2</string>

    <!--Beginner_Q3-->
    <string name="q3">What needs to be done before creating a hotspot using cmd?</string>
    <string name="q3_a1">Delete temp files</string>
    <string name="q3_a2">Clear the clipboard</string>
    <string name="q3_a3">Clear cache of the browser</string>
    <string name="q3_a4">Allow other network users to connect through the internet connection of the computer</string>
    <string name="q3_number">3</string>

    <!--Learn_Misc-->
    <string name="misc_header_1">Command Prompt Shortcuts</string>
    <string name="misc_header_2">How to Create an Undeletable Folder</string>
    <string name="misc_header_3">Get a Report on Your Laptop Battery</string>
    <string name="misc_header_4">How to Navigate Through Directories</string>

    <string name="misc_1_content">

        In the Command Prompt, right-click on the title bar to open the options and click Properties.
        \n\n
        Under the Options tab, find the section Edit Options and check the box next to Enable Ctrl key shortcuts.
        \n\n
        Copy selected text to clipboard:\n
        Ctrl + C / Ctrl + Insert
        \n\n
        Paste copied text: \n
        Ctrl + V / Shift + Insert
        \n\n
        Select all text in the current line (if there is no text in the current line, all text in the Command Prompt will be selected):\n
        Ctrl + A
        \n\n
        Move screen one line up/down (similar to scrolling):\n
        Ctrl + Up/Down
        \n\n
        Move screen one page up/down:\n
        Ctrl Page Up/Page Down
        \n\n
        Open Find window for searching through the Command Prompt:\n
        Ctrl F
        \n\n
        Enter Mark Mode (lets you select text with the mouse):\n
        Ctrl + M
        \n\n
        (In Mark Mode) Move cursor up, down, left, or right:\n
        Up/Down/Left/Right
        \n\n
        Move cursor up/down one line and select text:\n
        Shift+ Up/Down
        \n\n
        Move cursor left/right one character and select text:\n
        Shift + Left/Right
        \n\n
        Move cursor left/right one word and select text:\n
        Ctrl + Shift + Left/Right
        \n\n
        Move cursor up/down screen and select text:\n
        Shift + Page Up/Page Down
        \n\n
        Move cursor to the beginning/end of current line and select text:\n
        Shift + Home/End
        \n\n
        Move cursor to the beginning/end of screen buffer and select text and beginning/end of Command Prompt output:\n
        Ctrl + Shift + Home/End
    </string>

    <string name="misc_2_content">
        The basic concept behind this trick is the use of Keywords. Keywords are reserved words in any programming language that cannot be used as names of variables.
        \n\n
        Windows also uses certain keywords in its programming. Some of them are con, aux, Ipt1, Ipt2, Ipt3, Ipt 4, Ipt 5, Ipto, Ipt7, Ipt8 and Ipt9
        \n\n
        Open command prompt and change the root directory to location where you want to create an undeletable folder. For example,
        \n\n
        I want to create it in drive E. Now type following commands
        \n\n
        md con
        \n\n
        You can choose any keyword in place of con mentioned above. Now Windows will create an undeletable, unremovable folder in the drive you entered above.
        \n\n
        To Delete an undeletable folder, in command prompt, type
        \n\n
        rd con
        \n\n
        If it writes \the directory is not empty\' then type
        \n\n
        rd /S con
        \n\n
        Type Y.
        \n\n
        Now folder will successfully be deleted.
    </string>

    <string name="misc_3_content">
        Open command prompt. And to check battery energy, type
        \n\n
        powercfg/energy
        \n\n
        It will take 60 seconds to generate an energy report of your battery.
        \n\n
        To access the energy report, press
        \n\n
        Windows+R and type the location given below and this will open the report in web browser.
        \n\n
        C:\windows\system32 \ energy-report.html
        \n\n
        To check battery report, type the command in command prompt
        \n\n
        powercfg/batteryreport
        \n\n
        To view the Battery Report, press Windows+R and type the following location. The report will be displayed in web browser.
        \n\n
        C:\windows\system32 \battery-report.html
    </string>

    <string name="misc_4_content">
        Go to start menu and in the search box and type
        \n\n
        cmd
        \n\n
        Right click on command prompt icon and click on run as administrator.
        \n\n
        Press ok and your command prompt will operate successfully.
        \n\n
        To remove one path directory, just type cd..To add one directory, type cd followed by path\'s name like
        \n\n
        cd Users
        \n\n
        Note: Use cmd in run as administrator for command to operate successfully and always type command as it is so that it may not create any error.
    </string>

    <!--Learn_Security-->
    <string name="security_header_1">
        How to Create Recovery Images
        \n\n
        in Windows 8
    </string>
    <string name="security_header_2">How to Remove an Admin Password</string>
    <string name="security_header_3">How to Remove a Pattern Lock</string>
    <string name="security_header_4">How to Make Backup Files or Folders</string>
    <string name="security_header_5">How to Encrypt Files for Safety</string>
    <string name="security_header_6">How to Remove Virus</string>


    <string name="security_1_content">

        Create a destination folder for the custom image. For example, create a folder named "Refreshimage" on drive C.
        \n\n
        Open an elevated command prompt. To do this, follow these steps:
        \n\n
                On the Start page, type cmd, press and hold or right-click Command Prompt,
        \n
                and then tap or click Run as administrator.
        \n\n
        Type the following command, and then press Enter:
        \n
                recimg -CreateImage drive:\folder
        \n\n
        For example, if you create "C:\Refreshimage" in step 1, run the following command:
        \n
                Ctrl + A recimg -CreateImage C:\Refreshimage
    </string>

    <string name="security_2_content">
        Open up an elevated Command Prompt.
        \n\n
        At the Command Prompt, type the below command and press Enter.
        \n\n
            net user Administrator *
        \n\n
        When you\’re prompted to type new password, just press Enter twice and
        \n
        it will remove your Windows administrator password.
    </string>

    <string name="security_3_content">
        Make sure to set up ADB (Android Debug Bridge) on your computer.
        \n
        Download ADB files and drivers.
        \n\n
        You have enabled “USB DEBUGGING” on your phone.
        \n
        Go to Settings > Developer Option > USB debugging > Check the box.
        \n\n
        Now when you are done and sure that you are following the checklist, follow the given steps:
        \n\n
        (1) cable and make sure that you have an active pattern lock.
        \n\n
        (2) The SHIFT key and select “Open with Command Prompt”. The mentioned folder will be in Local Disk C.
        \n\n
            1. On the CMD window, type adb devices and then hit enter.
        \n
            2. Now type adb shell, then hit enter.
        \n
            3. The shell will open and after that type su ( superuser, you are now a root user).
        \n
            4. After entering, type rm/data/system/gesture.key then hit enter.
        \n
            5. Unplug your phone from PC and you are good to go.
    </string>

    <string name="security_4_content">
        Open Command Prompt and type the command:
        \n
            ”  Robocopy  “ (or xcopy for windows xp users)
        \n\n
        Then give a Space and enter the source path (folder) followed by the destination
        \n
        path  (folder)
        \n
        i.e., robocopy “Path of the source folder” “Path of the destination folder” and press enter.
        \n\n
            Example : robocopy "F:\\desktop\\windows 8\\My Great Project"
        \n
            "D:\\Backup"
    </string>

    <string name="security_5_content">
        Here is how to encrypt a certain folder on Windows 10:
        \n\n
            Right-click on the Command Prompt option and choose to run it as an administrator.
        \n\n
            If you want to apply changes to a certain folder, copy and paste the following
        \n
        into the Command Prompt window:
        \n
                cipher /e “here type the actual path of the folder you would like to encrypt”.
        \n\n

            If you want to apply encryption to a certain folder and all the files and subfolders it contains, here is the command you
        \n
        should use:
        \n
                cipher /e /s:”type the full path of the folder that is going to be encrypted”.
        \n\n
            Remember to press Enter after inputting one of the commands above.
        \n\n
            Close Command Prompt once you are done.
        \n\n\n
        How to encrypt a certain folder on Windows 10:
        \n\n
            Open an elevated Command Prompt window on your computer.
        \n\n
        Type the following:
        \n
        cipher /e “here input the full path of the file you want to encrypt”.
        \n\n
        Press Enter. Wait for the encryption process to finish and exit the Command
        \n
        Prompt window.
    </string>

    <string name="security_6_content">
        Open Command Prompt from search and run as an administrator.
        \n\n
            Type: D: and press Enter.
        \n\n
            Type: attrib and press Enter.
        \n
        You\'ll see autorun.inf virus files listed.
        \n\n
        To remove the virus using CMD, type into your command prompt:
        \n
            attrib -r -a -s -h *.* and press Enter.
        \n\n
        This will remove the Read Only, Archive, System and hidden file attribute from all the files.
        \n
        (*.* for all the files with all different types of file extensions).
        \n\n
            Type: del autorun.inf and hit enter to
        \n
        delete the files.
    </string>

    <!--button text-->
    <string name="question_button">Continue</string>
    <string name="read_button">Mark As Read</string>
	
	<string name="storage_content_01_text">
        Connect your write protected SD
        card or USB drive to your
        computer.\n\n

        Open Command Prompt and
        type the following commands
        and hit Enter.\n\n

        diskpart \n
        listdisk \n\n

        Here you\'ll be able to see a list
        of storage media connected to
        your computer. Notice your
        disk number and type.\n\n

        select disk 1\n\n

        Type your own disk number.In
        my case it is 1. Make sure you
        enter the number correctly and
        don\'t end up changing the
        attributes  of your internal hard
        drive. Now type the following
        commands.\n\n

        attributes disk\n
        attributes disk clear readonly\n
        exit\n\n

        Now disk attributes will clear
        and you will now get out of
        the diskpart utility.\n\n

        Now you are done with
        disabling write protection in
        your removable drive.

    </string>

    <string name="storage_header_1">Remove write protection</string>
    <string name="storage_header_2">Hide a local disk drive</string>
    <string name="storage_header_3">Make a back up of files and folders</string>
    <string name="storage_header_4">Make any USB drive bootable </string>
	
	<!--Learn_Network-->
    <string name="network_header_1">Create a wi-fi hotspot for others</string>
    <string name="network_header_2">Wi-fi password of used network on PC</string>
    <string name="network_header_3">Trace any friend IP address and know location </string>
    <string name="network_header_4">How to find IP address of any website</string>
	
	<string name="network_1_content">

To create Wi-Fi hotspot from the command \n
prompt: Before opening the Command \n
Prompt. Open Control Panel, \n
Find Change adapter settings in the Network and Sharing option.\n
Click on the connection you are using and \n
click on Properties. \n\n\n

        find the sharing tab and check the option \n
"Allow other network users to connect \n
through this computer\'s internet connection" \n\n

        Open the Command Prompt with admin \n
istrative privileges and enter the following \n
command. In place of \'anmy\' you write \n
hotspot name(any name) and in place of \n
\'qwerty\' you write your own password. \n\n

        netsh wlan set hostednetwork mode=allow \n
ssid=and key qwerty \n\n

        After it\'s enabled, enter to start wi-fi \n

netsh wlan start hostednetwork
    </string>


    <string name="network_2_content">

        If you are connecting to Wi-Fi networks \n
with your computer, your operating system \n
usually saves the passwords of the networks\n
you are connected to.\n\n\n


         first run a command prompt with\n
 run as administrator.\n
 Now type - netsh wlan show profiles\n\n

In a list of networks, look for the\n
network, you want the password of. \n
Suppose I choose \'isro\' from\n
my network list. \n
Now type-\n
netsh wlan show profiles isro key clear\n\n

        Now in the list, where you find \n
\'key content\' written, it is the password \n
of that wifi network.\n


    </string>

    <string name="network_3_content">
        First you got to find out the IP address of\n
        that User.\n
        To do so we will be not be using \'netstat\' \n
        command in windows because this method\n
        doesn\'t work nowadays. We can\'t find the \n
        IP address of a facebook user using cmd\n
        nowadays. \n\n
        However there is other way round using two \n
        websites.So we will be doing that.\n\n\n
        Go to the site: blasze.com\n
        There in the box you type any website\'s url.\n
        Suppose I typed \'facebook.com\'. Now the\n
        link information will be shown.\n\n
        Copy the \'tracking link\' and make the\n
        user(whose ip address you want to find)\n
        access that link through chat or anything.\n\n
        Once he clicks on that link, copy your \'access\n
        code\' from link information, go back and\n
        paste your access code in the box and enter.\n\n
        You will see the information in \'access logs\'\n
        little below. You will find his/her ip address\n
        along will computer or phone details.See the\n
        images below\n
    </string>

    <string name="network_32_content">
The next step is to trace that user, using his\n
IP address.To do so we will be using IP tracer\n
service. Go to the below address and paste\n
the IP address in the box.\n
http://www.ip-adress.com\n
/ip address to location/\n\n

It will show you all the information about that\n
user along with his ISP and a Location in the\n
MAP However exact location is not shown.\n

    </string>

    <string name="network_4_content">
Open command prompt and type either \'ping\n
or \'tracert\' depending upon which command\n
you are going to use, followed by URL of the\n
website you want to ping. Like any one of\n
following\n
ping fossbytes.com\n
tracert fossbytes.com\n\n

Press Enter and wait for the ping results. The\n
first line after your command should contain\n
the desired IP address.\n

    </string>

    <!--experience_level-->
    <string name="relative_header">Relative Progress</string>

</resources>
